[SPEAKER_00] English 1
[SPEAKER_01] English 2
[SPEAKER_02] English 3
[SPEAKER_00] English 4
[SPEAKER_00] English 5
[SPEAKER_00] English 6
[SPEAKER_00] English 7
[SPEAKER_01] English 6
[SPEAKER_01] English 7
[SPEAKER_01] English 8
[SPEAKER_02] English 11
[SPEAKER_02] English 12
[SPEAKER_01] English 13
[SPEAKER_01] English 14
[SPEAKER_01] English 15
[SPEAKER_02] English 16
[SPEAKER_02] English 17
[SPEAKER_01] English 18
[SPEAKER_01] English 9
[SPEAKER_00] English 20
[SPEAKER_00] English 21
[SPEAKER_00] English 22
[SPEAKER_00] English 23
[SPEAKER_00] English 10
[SPEAKER_00] English 25
[SPEAKER_00] English 26
[SPEAKER_00] English 11
[SPEAKER_00] English 12
[SPEAKER_00] English 29
[SPEAKER_00] English 30
[SPEAKER_00] English 13
[SPEAKER_00] English 32
[SPEAKER_01] English 33
[SPEAKER_00] English 14
[SPEAKER_00] English 15
[SPEAKER_00] English 16
[SPEAKER_00] English 17
[SPEAKER_01] English 38
[SPEAKER_00] English 39
[SPEAKER_00] English 18
[SPEAKER_01] English 19
[SPEAKER_02] English 20
[SPEAKER_02] English 43
[SPEAKER_02] English 44
[SPEAKER_01] English 45
[SPEAKER_02] English 46
[SPEAKER_02] English 47
[SPEAKER_01] English 48
[SPEAKER_02] English 49
[SPEAKER_00] English 50
[SPEAKER_00] English 51
[SPEAKER_00] English 52
[SPEAKER_01] English 53
[SPEAKER_01] English 54
[SPEAKER_00] English 55
[SPEAKER_00] English 21
[SPEAKER_01] English 57
[SPEAKER_00] English 58
[SPEAKER_01] English 59
[SPEAKER_00] English 60
[SPEAKER_02] English 22
[SPEAKER_00] English 62
[SPEAKER_02] English 23
[SPEAKER_02] English 64
[SPEAKER_01] English 24
[SPEAKER_02] English 66
[SPEAKER_02] English 67
[SPEAKER_02] English 68
[SPEAKER_01] English 69
[SPEAKER_01] English 70
[SPEAKER_00] English 71
[SPEAKER_00] English 25
[SPEAKER_01] English 73
[SPEAKER_00] English 74
[SPEAKER_00] English 75
[SPEAKER_00] English 76
[SPEAKER_00] English 77
English 78
[SPEAKER_00] English 79
[SPEAKER_01] English 80
[SPEAKER_01] English 81
[SPEAKER_01] English 82
[SPEAKER_02] English 83
[SPEAKER_01] English 84
[SPEAKER_02] English 85
[SPEAKER_02] English 86
[SPEAKER_00] English 87
[SPEAKER_00] English 88
[SPEAKER_02] English 89
[SPEAKER_02] English 90
[SPEAKER_02] English 91
[SPEAKER_02] English 92
[SPEAKER_01] English 93
[SPEAKER_00] English 94
[SPEAKER_00] English 95
[SPEAKER_01] English 26
[SPEAKER_01] English 97
[SPEAKER_02] English 98
[SPEAKER_01] English 99
[SPEAKER_02] English 27
[SPEAKER_01] English 28
[SPEAKER_01] English 102
[SPEAKER_01] English 103
[SPEAKER_02] English 104
[SPEAKER_02] English 29
[SPEAKER_01] English 106
[SPEAKER_02] English 107
[SPEAKER_01] English 108
[SPEAKER_00] English 109
[SPEAKER_01] English 110
[SPEAKER_00] English 30
[SPEAKER_01] English 112
[SPEAKER_01] English 113
[SPEAKER_02] English 114
[SPEAKER_02] English 115
[SPEAKER_02] English 31
[SPEAKER_00] English 117
[SPEAKER_00] English 32
[SPEAKER_00] English 33
[SPEAKER_02] English 34
[SPEAKER_02] English 35
[SPEAKER_02] English 36
[SPEAKER_01] English 37
[SPEAKER_01] English 124
[SPEAKER_02] English 125
[SPEAKER_01] English 126
[SPEAKER_01] English 127
[SPEAKER_02] English 128
[SPEAKER_02] English 129
[SPEAKER_02] English 130
[SPEAKER_00] English 131
[SPEAKER_02] English 132
[SPEAKER_01] English 133
[SPEAKER_01] English 38
English 135
[SPEAKER_02] English 136
[SPEAKER_02] English 137
[SPEAKER_02] English 138
[SPEAKER_00] English 139
[SPEAKER_00] English 140
[SPEAKER_00] English 141
[SPEAKER_00] English 142
[SPEAKER_00] English 143
[SPEAKER_00] English 144
[SPEAKER_01] English 145
[SPEAKER_01] English 146
[SPEAKER_02] English 147
[SPEAKER_01] English 148
[SPEAKER_00] English 39
[SPEAKER_00] English 150
[SPEAKER_00] English 151
[SPEAKER_02] English 152
[SPEAKER_01] English 153
[SPEAKER_02] English 154
[SPEAKER_01] English 155
[SPEAKER_01] English 156
[SPEAKER_00] English 157
[SPEAKER_00] English 158
[SPEAKER_01] English 159
[SPEAKER_00] English 160
[SPEAKER_01] English 161
[SPEAKER_02] English 162
[SPEAKER_00] English 163
[SPEAKER_00] English 164
[SPEAKER_00] English 165
[SPEAKER_01] English 166
[SPEAKER_00] English 167
[SPEAKER_00] English 168
[SPEAKER_00] English 169
[SPEAKER_00] English 170
[SPEAKER_00] English 171
[SPEAKER_01] English 172
[SPEAKER_00] English 173
English 174
[SPEAKER_00] English 175
[SPEAKER_00] English 176
[SPEAKER_00] English 177
[SPEAKER_01] English 178
[SPEAKER_00] English 179
[SPEAKER_01] English 180
[SPEAKER_01] English 181
[SPEAKER_01] English 182
[SPEAKER_01] English 183
[SPEAKER_01] English 184
[SPEAKER_01] English 185
[SPEAKER_00] English 186
[SPEAKER_01] English 187
[SPEAKER_00] English 188
[SPEAKER_00] English 189
[SPEAKER_00] English 190
[SPEAKER_01] English 191
[SPEAKER_01] English 192
[SPEAKER_01] English 193
[SPEAKER_01] English 194
[SPEAKER_02] English 195
[SPEAKER_02] English 196
[SPEAKER_02] English 197
[SPEAKER_02] English 198
[SPEAKER_01] English 199
English 200
English 201
English 202
English 203
English 204
English 205
English 206
English 40
[SPEAKER_02] English 208
[SPEAKER_02] English 209
[SPEAKER_02] English 210
[SPEAKER_00] English 211
[SPEAKER_00] English 212
[SPEAKER_02] English 213
[SPEAKER_02] English 214
[SPEAKER_01] English 215
[SPEAKER_01] English 216
English 217
English 218
English 219
[SPEAKER_02] English 220
[SPEAKER_01] English 41
[SPEAKER_02] English 222
[SPEAKER_02] English 223
[SPEAKER_02] English 224
[SPEAKER_02] English 225
[SPEAKER_01] English 226
[SPEAKER_00] English 227
[SPEAKER_00] English 228
[SPEAKER_00] English 42
[SPEAKER_00] English 230
[SPEAKER_00] English 231
[SPEAKER_00] English 232
[SPEAKER_00] English 233
[SPEAKER_00] English 234
English 235
[SPEAKER_00] English 236
[SPEAKER_00] English 237
English 238
[SPEAKER_00] English 239
[SPEAKER_00] English 240
[SPEAKER_00] English 241
[SPEAKER_00] English 43
[SPEAKER_00] English 44
[SPEAKER_00] English 45
[SPEAKER_00] English 245
[SPEAKER_00] English 46
[SPEAKER_02] English 47
[SPEAKER_02] English 248
[SPEAKER_00] English 48
[SPEAKER_00] English 250
[SPEAKER_00] English 49
[SPEAKER_00] English 50
[SPEAKER_02] English 51
[SPEAKER_00] English 254
[SPEAKER_01] English 255
[SPEAKER_01] English 52
[SPEAKER_02] English 257
[SPEAKER_02] English 258
[SPEAKER_00] English 53
[SPEAKER_00] English 260
[SPEAKER_00] English 54
[SPEAKER_00] English 55
[SPEAKER_00] English 56
[SPEAKER_00] English 264
[SPEAKER_00] English 265
[SPEAKER_01] English 57
[SPEAKER_02] English 267
[SPEAKER_02] English 268
English 269
[SPEAKER_02] English 58
[SPEAKER_01] English 271
[SPEAKER_02] English 272
[SPEAKER_02] English 273